kaleidescape.com 2019-12-11

# Kaleidescape Privacy Policy

Kaleidescape Privacy Policy
Kaleidescape takes your privacy seriously. This Privacy Policy describes how we treat personal
information that we collect and receive about you and your use of your Kaleidescape System
("System"), the Kaleidescape Movie Guide and Music Guide Services, Kaleidescape mobile
applications (e.g. Kaleidescape App for iPad, and the Kaleidescape App for iPhone), the
Kaleidescape Movie Store, and our other websites.
This Privacy Policy supplements and is incorporated into the Kaleidescape Service & License
Agreement (“SLA”). This Privacy Policy constitutes the entire agreement between you and
Kaleidescape concerning the subject matter herein, and your use of kaleidescape.com,
Kaleidescape mobile applications, or your acceptance of the Kaleidescape Service & License
Agreement will signify your acceptance of this Privacy Policy.
To provide you with a better, more satisfying experience, Kaleidescape collects and uses certain
types of information, as described below. Kaleidescape does not intend to disclose to any third
party, except as provided below, any personal information, including what CDs, DVDs, Blu- ray
discs, or other media formats you — as an individual or household — have purchased, imported,
downloaded, or viewed with your System.
Types of Information Collected
•    Kaleidescape collects certain personal information when you activate your System, such as
     your name, address, telephone number, and email address. Kaleidescape collects additional
     information from time to time, such as the serial numbers of the components of your System
     and the software versions and options used by them.
•    Kaleidescape automatically collects and maintains diagnostic and usage information from
     your System whenever it is connected to the Internet, for the purposes of quality control,
     technical troubleshooting, marketing, and the development of new features, products, and
     services. Diagnostic and usage information includes a detailed record of the operating history
     of your System, such as browser interface settings, CD, DVD, and Blu-ray imports,
     downloads from the Kaleidescape Movie Store, user inputs and response times (including
     details about movies played), disk errors or failures, disk space use, component
     temperatures, and information entered into the browser interface. Diagnostic and usage
     information also includes the serial numbers of the components of your System and their IP
     addresses.
•    Kaleidescape automatically collects IP addresses and website usage information from you
     when you visit our website. This information helps us evaluate how our visitors use and
     navigate our website on an aggregate basis, including the number and frequency of visitors
     to each Web page, and the lengths of their visits.
•    Kaleidescape also collects IP address information from you to determine your geolocation,
     which is used to determine the applicable Movie Store territory.
•    Kaleidescape collects data using Google Analytics for Display Advertisers, including Google
     Analytics for Demographics and Interest Reporting. The data collected may be used to
     perform techniques such as market segmentation, remarketing and A/B testing, in order to
     provide more relevant products and services. Kaleidescape does not alter its data collection
     based on the presence of a ‘do not track’ request configured in your browser; however, you
     may opt-out from Google Analytics by following the instructions here:
     https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/.
•    Kaleidescape collects and maintains diagnostic and usage information from its mobile
     applications. for the purposes of technical troubleshooting, marketing, and the
     development of new features, products, and services. Diagnostic and usage information
     includes details on Movie Store browsing, searching and purchase transactions,
     Kaleidescape player control, as well as usage of the notification center, downloads
     management and configuration settings features of the application. Kaleidescape uses a
     third-party tool called Amplitude, operated by Amplitude, Inc., to help collect, store,
     process, and manage diagnostic and usage information for mobile applications.

How We Use Information Collected
We may use information in the following ways:
•    For the purposes for which you specifically provided the information including, for
     example, to provide a service that you desire, to troubleshoot your System, or to send
     emails that you have requested.
•    To send you email notifications about new or existing products and services, such
     as software upgrades.
•    To enhance existing features, products and services, or to develop new features, products
     and services.
•    To better understand our customers, distribution channel, and market.
•    To provide third parties with aggregate information (that will not identify you or your
     household) about our user base and usage patterns, including movies played.
•    To allow us to make recommendations and to improve your experience and that of others
     based on your usage characteristics and preferences, and those of other Kaleidescape
     users.
•    To fulfill any other reasonable business purpose that Kaleidescape deems to be desirable.
•    When we believe in good faith that it is necessary to release information to comply with the
     law, enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements, or protect the rights,
     property, or safety of Kaleidescape, our employees, our users, or others. This includes
     exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and
     credit risk reduction.
•    We may choose to buy or sell company assets. In these types of transactions, customer
     information is often a business asset that is transferred. Moreover, if the company sells some
     of its assets, or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information would be one
     of the assets that is transferred to or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such
     transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of the company may continue to use your personal
     information as set forth in this policy.
Except as specifically set forth in this Privacy Policy, we will not share your personally-identifiable
information outside of Kaleidescape.
We may disclose and use personally-identifiable information to resolve disputes, troubleshoot
problems, enforce our Kaleidescape Service & License Agreement (for example, when necessary
to protect our or a third-party's intellectual property or proprietary rights). We may also disclose
personally-identifiable information when we, in our sole discretion, believe it is necessary or
appropriate, in connection with a sale or transfer of some or all of our assets, or when we, in good
faith, believe that the law requires us to do so.
We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf including, without
limitation, packaging, mailing and delivering products and services, answering customer
questions about products and services, processing registrations, analyzing our market, and
designing future products. We will only provide those companies with the information they need
to deliver their services, and they are prohibited from using that information for any other
purpose.
Your information may be stored and processed in the United States or any country in which
Kaleidescape or its subsidiaries or agents maintain a presence; you consent to any such
transfer of your personal information outside of your country and to the usage of your
information as described in this Privacy Policy.
Minors (individuals under the age of 18) are not authorized to have accounts with Kaleidescape,
and we do not knowingly collect information from Minors. Use of your System (as defined in the
SLA) and other actions by Minors concerning or when using your System is your responsibility
and you agree that their actions shall be attributed to you and/or the owner or authorized user of
such System.

Security of your Personal Information
Kaleidescape is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a
variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from
unauthorized access, use or disclosure. For example, your personal information will be stored
on computer servers with limited access that are located in controlled facilities. When we
transmit sensitive information (such as a credit card number) over the Internet, we protect it
through encryption.
Policy Modifications
We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will post any changes here.
Technical Problems
Even though Kaleidescape has taken steps to ensure that your personal information will not be
collected, used, or disclosed by Kaleidescape except as set forth by this Privacy Policy, technical
mistakes are possible. If such a mistake takes place, we will take commercially-reasonable steps
to correct it.
Contact Kaleidescape
If you would like to make suggestions or find out more about our privacy practices, please send
email to legal@kaleidescape.com.
This Privacy Policy was last updated on August 28, 2018.
